Contact

jeanette.pennick@memorialhe rmann.org

www.linkedin.com/in/jeanettepennick-msn-rn-bc-cmsrn-ne-bcnea-bc-5623018a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Microsoft Excel Microsoft Word

Certifications

Executive Six Sigma Black Belt RN-BC, NE-BC, NEA-BC, CMSRN

Jeanette Pennick, MSN, RN-BC, CMSRN, NE-BC, NEA-BC

Director of Emergency Services at HCA Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Passionate Director of Emergency Services with experience in leadership, development and performance improvement in medical-surgical, ICU and ER. Six sigma black belt, ANCC certified as nurse executive with MSN focused in Leadership from University of Texas at Arlington. Nursing is my passion and my purpose.

Experience

The University of Texas at Arlington Critical Care Nursing Professor October 2018 - Present (1 year 9 months) Arlington, Texas

Adjunct Critical Care Clinical Professor CVICU, ICU, ER

HCA

Director Of Emergency Services August 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months)

Memorial Hermann Health System 6 years 9 months

Director (ER, ICU, RT, Operations)
January 2015 - February 2017 (2 years 2 months)

Clinical Manager II
June 2010 - October 2015 (5 years 5 months)

Houston Methodist
9 years 7 months
Emergency Room Nurse

June 2008 - December 2013 (5 years 7 months)

HR/OD, Organizational Development Training Specialist

Page 1 of 3

June 2006 - June 2008 (2 years 1 month)

Registered Nurse-Cardiothoracic June 2004 - December 2006 (2 years 7 months) Methodist Houston

Cardiovascular and Thoracic

University General Hospital
PRN House Supervisor
June 2010 - July 2012 (2 years 2 months)

University of Alberta Hospital
Registered Nurse
January 2001 - January 2004 (3 years 1 month)
U of A Critical Care Float

Caritas

LPN

January 1999 - January 2001 (2 years 1 month)

Dr. Lundardon Professional Corp Business Office Manager January 1998 - January 2000 (2 years 1 month)

Sunglass Hut International Multi Unit Manager January 1996 - December 1998 (3 years)

Dynamite Clothing
Assistant Manager
January 1994 - March 1996 (2 years 3 months)

Ardene Manager March 1992 - February 1994 (2 years)

Education

University of Texas at Arlington MSN, Leadership · (2012 - 2014)

University of Alberta

BScN with Academic Distinction, Nursing · (2002 - 2004)

Grant MacEwan University Nursing, Nursing · (1999 - 2001)